致敬斯坦·李
哈拉
克里文明首都
你知道现在几点吗
Do you know what time it is?
睡不着
Can't sleep.
有药片治失眠的
There are tabs for that.
没错  但吃了我不就睡着了
Yeah, but then I'd be sleeping.
又做梦了
Dreams again?
想打架吗
Wanna fight?
我滑倒了
I slipped.
是啊  你滑倒了
Right, you slipped
因为我一拳打在了你脸上
as a result of me punching you in the face.
你打到我脸的时候
I was already slipping
我就已经要滑倒了
when you happened to punch me in the face.
这两件事毫不相关
The two events were not related.
跟我说说这个梦
Tell me about this dream.
-有什么新内容吗  -没有
- Anything new? - No.
你必须放下过去
You have to let go of the past.
我不记得我的过去了
I don't remember my past.
这让你产生怀疑
It's causing you doubt,
怀疑让你有弱点
and doubt makes you vulnerable.
控制住
Control it.
如果你再次失控
Lose control again,
就得去找至高智慧密谈了
and you'll have to commune with the Supreme Intelligence.
对于战士而言  情绪是最危险的
There's nothing more dangerous to a warrior than emotion.
幽默使人分心
Humor is a distraction.
而愤怒
And anger?
愤怒只会帮助你的敌人
Anger only serves the enemy.
距最后一次斯库鲁侵袭已过去了120天
One hundred twenty days since the last Skrull attack.
有人见过
Has anyone ever seen
至高智慧的真面目吗
what the Supreme Intelligence really looks like?
没人能看到至高智慧的真面目
No one can look upon the Supreme Intelligence in its true form.
你知道的
You know that.
我们的潜意识会选择我们所能看到的形象
Our subconscious chooses the way they appear to us.
因此它是神圣的
So it's sacred.
也是私密的
It's personal.
克里人绝对不会泄露这个秘密
No Kree divulges it, ever.
你会看到谁
Who do you see?
-你哥哥吗  -不是
- Your brother? - No.
-父亲  -不是
- Father? - No.
-你以前的指挥官  -弗斯
- Your old commander? - Vers.
你看到的是我  对吧
It's me you see, isn't it?
我知道你想干什么
I see what you're trying to do.
-这招有用吗  -有用
- Is it working? - Yes.
但你别想转移话题
But you won't succeed in changing the subject.
如果你不希望我使用这力量
What is the point of giving me these...
那还何必把它给我
if you don't want me to use them?
我希望你使用这力量
I want you to use them.
至高智慧让我负责
The Supreme Intelligence gave me a responsibility...
教会你如何使用这力量
of showing you how to use them.
我知道怎么用
I know how.
如果你真会用
Yeah, if that were true,
就能不用它也可以打倒我了
you'd be able to knock me down without them.
控制你的冲动
Control your impulses.
不要用这儿  而是用这儿
Stop using this, start using this.
我希望你成为最好的自己
I want you to be the best version of yourself.
至高智慧
克里文明的人工智能领袖
弗斯
Vers.
至高智慧
Intelligence.
你的指挥官坚称你已可以服役
Your commander insists that you're fit to serve.
是的
I am.
你在苦苦纠结你的情绪
You struggle with your emotions...
和你的过去  这助长了它们
with your past, which fuels them.
你只是斯库鲁扩张的受害者之一
You are just one victim of the Skrull expansion...
几世纪以来  他们一直威胁着我们的文明
that has threatened our civilization for centuries.
这些卧底暗中潜入
Imposters who silently infiltrate...
然后占领我们的星球
then take over our planets.
你只记得些许可怕之事
Horrors that you remember...
而大部分已忘却
and so much that you do not.
我的人生一片空白
It's all blank. My life.
你的形象应该是
You're supposed to take the form
我最钦佩的人
of who I most admire...
但我甚至都不记得这人是我的什么人了
but I don't even remember who this person was to me.
或许这样也好
Perhaps this is a mercy
让你免受更多痛苦
sparing you from a deeper pain.
让你放开手脚去做所有克里人该做之事
Freeing you to do what all Kree must...
将人民的需求置于自身之上
Put your people's needs before your own.
我们赐予了你伟大的赠礼
We've given you a great gift.
一个为全体克里人而战的机会
The chance to fight for the good of all Kree.
我想要尽忠
I want to serve.
那就学会自控
Then master yourself.
赐予你的也能收回
What was given can be taken away.
我不会让你失望的
I won't let you down.
我们很快就会见分晓了
We'll know soon enough.
你有一项任务
You have a mission.
尽职尽忠  恪守荣耀
Serve well, and with honor.
一定是出大事了
This can't be good.
肯定又是斯库鲁侵袭
Must be another Skrull attack.
反正是大事
Whatever it is, it's big.
有斯库鲁人模仿过你吗
Has a Skrull ever simmed you?
有过一次
Once.
-让我深感不安  -为什么
- It was deeply disturbing. - Why?
因为当我凝视死敌之时
Because I stared into the face of my mortal enemy...
看到的却是我自己
and the face staring back was my own.
也许你要是再帅点
Maybe if you were more attractive,
就不会那么不安了
then it would be less disturbing.
你觉得自己很幽默  可我并不觉得好笑
You think you're funny, but I'm not laughing.
你从来不笑
You never laugh.
我只是笑不外露
I laugh on the inside.
我现在并没笑
I'm not doing that now.
说来好笑  因为客观来讲
It's funny 'cause, objectively speaking,
你还挺帅的
you're quite handsome.
多谢
Well, thank you.
好了  小队  别闹了
Listen up, team. Knock it off.
好
All right.
准备去
Prepare for...
搜救我们的间谍  索拉
a search and rescue of our spy, Soh-Larr.
斯库鲁人又入侵了一个边境星球
The Skrulls have invaded yet another border planet.
这次是托法
This time, Torfa.
索拉发来了警告
Soh-Larr sent us a warning.
但信号遭到了拦截  他的身份也曝光了
The signal was intercepted, and his cover's blown.
斯库鲁将军塔罗斯
The Skrull general, Talos,
派了击杀小队去找他
has sent kill units to find him.
如果他们在我们之前找到他
Should they reach him before we do...
那他这三年来收集的情报
the intelligence he's acquired over three years
就等于送给他们了
is as good as theirs.
指控者将轰炸南部这里的一个斯库鲁要塞
The Accusers will bomb a Skrull stronghold here in the south.
我们潜入  找到索拉
We slip in, we locate Soh-Larr...
然后出来  神不知鬼不觉
and we get out, leaving them none the wiser.
托法人
The Torfan populace.
我们不要干扰他们
We are not to interfere with them,
也不要被他们缠住
nor them with us.
我们任务的机密性是第一位的
Nothing compromises the security of our mission.
务必万分小心
Proceed with caution.
撤离他前遵循规程
Follow protocol before extracting him.
此次任务很危险
This is a dangerous mission.
我们要做好加入大集体的准备
We must all be ready to join the Collective
若那是我们今日的命数
if that is our fate today.
为全体克里人而战
For the good of all Kree.
For the good of all Kree!
托法
克里边境星球
弗斯  追踪索拉的信标
Vers, track Soh-Larr's beacon.
阿特拉斯  米涅瓦  找到高地
Att-Lass, Minn-Erva, find elevation.
外围有本地人
Locals on the periphery.
可能有十几个
Maybe a dozen.
米涅瓦
Minn-Erva?
收到吗  有人收到吗
Do you read me? Does anybody copy?
重复
Repeat.
他的信标信号在那个寺庙里  我们走
His beacon's coming from that temple. Let's move.
不  这里太适合伏击了
No. This is a perfect spot for an ambush.
只有一条路进出
Only one way in, only one way out.
我们可以绕过本地人
We can get past the locals.
我们都不能确定他们是否真是本地人
We don't know if they are locals.
太冒险
Too risky.
你不用跟我一起去  我可以自己去
You don't have to go with me. I'll go alone.
不  不行
No, you won't.
好吧  我们不要走远
Right. We keep a close radius.
如果断联  就回氦核飞船碰头
We lose comms, we meet back at the Helion.
走吧
Come on.
阿特拉斯  你看到了吗
Att-Lass, you getting this?
收到  看到了
Copy. I see them.
退后
Get back!
指挥官
Commander?
退后  退后
Get back! Back!
米涅瓦  你看到了吗
Minn-Erva? Do you have eyes on this?
拦住他们  米涅瓦
Keep them back. Minn-Erva?
有人收到吗
Does anybody copy?
我不想伤害你
I don't wanna hurt you.
别过来
Keep back!
Stay back!
他们是本地人  我发现两具尸体  没有绿血
They're locals. I found two dead. No green.
他们只是饿了
They're just starving.
HGX78
Hgx-78.
TRT79  VVX6
Trt79-vvx6.
退后
Get back.
斯库鲁人
Skrulls!
弗斯
Vers!
弗斯  斯库鲁人
Vers? Skrulls.
是埋伏
It's an ambush.
敌舰
Incoming!
回氦核飞船去
Back to the Helion.
弗斯  收到吗
Vers. Do you copy?
回氦核飞船去
Back to the Helion.
回复  弗斯
Come in. Vers.
你怎么会知道密码
How did you know the code?
我可以告诉你我的秘密
How about I tell you my secret...
但你先说你的
when you've told me yours?
敞开她吧
Let's open her up.
我们在哪
Where are we?
就绪
Stand by.
你想什么呢[脑袋在哪]
Where's your head at?
想云彩[胡思乱想]  你呢
In the clouds. Where's yours?
在我肩膀上
On my shoulders.
要让这些男的见识一下我们的本事
About to show these boys how we do it.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
更高  更远  更快啊  亲爱的
Higher, further, faster, baby.
没错
That's right.
这不对
This can't be right.
再往前倒
Go back even further.
你开太快了  你得慢点
You're going too fast! You need to go slow!
这人是谁  我们找对...
Who is this person? Are we in the right...?
你怎么想的
What the hell are you thinking?
你不该来这里
You don't belong out here!
我们好像倒得太多了
I think we went back too far.
你让他开了
You let him drive.
我试试吧
Let me try something.
放弃吧
Give up already!
你不该来这里
You don't belong out here!
你不够强壮
You're not strong enough.
你会害死自己的
You'll kill yourself.
他们绝不会让你飞的
They'll never let you fly.
只有我一个人看糊涂了吗
Am I the only one that's confused here?
你是个好飞行员
You're a decent pilot.
但你太情绪化
But you're too emotional.
你知道那为什么叫驾驶舱[屌坑]吧
You do know why they call it a cockpit, don't you?
一声贯穿宇宙的巨响  震动了月亮
A huge rumble throughout the cosmos shook the moon...
太阳  和天上的星星
and the sun and the stars in the sky.
于是
And so,
小阿露蒂整夜飞上天空
little Alouette flew up throughout the night.
你看到她了吗  那是小阿露蒂
Did you see her? It's Alouette.
给我进来  该吃饭了
Get your butts inside, it's time to eat.
准备起飞  捣蛋中尉
Prepare for takeoff, Lieutenant Trouble.
有趣的记忆
Charming memory.
等等
Hang on.
我好像找到了
I think I've got it.
咕咕喜欢你
Goose likes you.
她一般不怎么亲近人的
She doesn't typically take to people.
你起得好早
Early start to your morning.
其实是晚上熬夜了
Late night, actually.
还有工作  我就睡不着
I can't sleep when there's work to do.
耳熟吗
Sound familiar?
我从不觉得飞行是工作
Flying your planes never feels like work.
风景很棒  是吧
Wonderful view, isn't it?
我更喜欢上面的风景
I prefer the view from up there.
你很快就能上去了  王牌
You'll get there soon enough, Ace.
等等  就是她  倒回去
Wait! Wait, wait! That's her. Get her back.
就绪
Stand by.
耳熟吗
Sound familiar?
风景很棒  是吧
Wonderful view, isn't it?
我更喜欢上面的风景
I prefer the view from up there.
你很快就能上去了  王牌
You'll get there soon enough, Ace.
她衣服上写着什么
What's that on her shirt?
我看不清
I couldn't read it.
风景很棒  是吧
Wonderful view, isn't it?
我更喜欢上面的风景
I prefer the view from up there.
-你很快就能上去了  王牌  -集中精神
- You'll get there soon enough, Ace. - Focus.
什么
Excuse me?
-你很快就能上去了  王牌  -往下看
- You'll get there soon enough, Ace. - Look down.
集中精神
Focus.
"飞马计划  温迪·劳森博士"  就是她
"Pegasus. Dr. Wendy Lawson." That's her.
你也能听到吗
Do you hear that, too?
定位了吗
Do we have her location?
找到了
Got it.
追踪劳森  直到找到能量信号
Now track Lawson until we find the energy signature.
有趣
Interesting.
等等
Hold on.
倒回到这之前  回去
Go back right before this. Go back.
那可不是米格  劳森
That's no MiG, Lawson.
就是这个  让我看看你要去哪
This is it. Now let me see where you're headed.
没错  看看坐标
That's right. Look at the coordinates.
集中精神
Focus.
请敞开头脑
Open, please.
就这样  就这样
That's it. That's it.
快看到了
You're almost there.
快看到了  别抵抗
You're almost there. Don't fight it.
集中精神
Focus!
把她拉回来  快点
Get her back! Get her back now!
这没道理
This doesn't make any sense.
我们拿到任何可以行动的情报了吗
Do we have any information we can act on?
只知道劳森在C53星球上某处
Just that Lawson was somewhere on planet C-53.
我们这就去
We're on our way.
那就再继续深挖
Then dig, dig, dig deeper.
劳森能带我们找到光速引擎
Lawson is our link to that light-speed engine!
和我们想要的一切
And everything we're after.
刚刚那下有用
That did something.
再来
Try that again.
不行
Not yet!
你对我做了什么
What did you do to me?
我们只是想要点情报
Now we're just after a little information.
你往我脑袋里放了什么
What did you put in my head?
那都是本就存在的
Nothing that wasn't already there.
但那些不是我的记忆
But those aren't my memories.
是啊  就像嗑错了药  是吧
Yeah, it's like a bad trip, isn't it?
怪不得你稀里糊涂的
I'm not surprised you can't keep it straight.
他们真把你祸害得不轻
They really did a number on you.
少跟我玩心理战
Enough of your mind games.
你想要什么
What do you want?
我们在找一位劳森博士
We're looking for the location of a Dr. Lawson...
和她的光速引擎
and her light-speed engine.
我不认识什么劳森博士
I don't know any Dr. Lawson.
是吗  那她为什么在你脑袋里
Really? Then why is she in your head?
你们不会刚好知道
You guys wouldn't happen to know
这玩意怎么拿下来吧
how these things come off, would ya?
不吗
No?
好吧
Fine.
你知道那为什么叫...
You do know why they call it a...
这就走了
You leaving so soon?
我们才刚认识
We're just getting to know each other.
百视达
C53星球
地球家园
弗斯呼叫星际战队指挥部  收到吗
Vers to Starforce command, do you read me?
喂
Hello?
收到吗
Do you copy?
我是弗斯  克里星际战队的
I'm Vers. Kree Starforce.
这里是C53吗
Is this C-53?
你听懂了吗  我的宇宙翻译器好使吧
Do you understand me? Is my universal translator working?
嗯  我听懂了
Yeah. I understand you.
好的
Oh, good.
你负责这一带的安全吗
Are you in charge of security for this district?
算是吧  影院有自己的保安
Sort of. Uh, the movie theater has its own guy.
我去哪能找到通讯设备
Where can I find communications equipment?
睿侠
谢谢
Thank you.
追踪飞行舱  找到那姑娘
Track the pod. Find the girl.
她知道的情报比自己以为的多
She knows more than she knows.
这个我要了
This one's taken.
拜托
Come on.
弗斯
Vers?
证实身份  CTC39
Verify. CTC-39.
GRXV1600
Grxv-1600.
我很好  多谢关心
And I'm fine, thank you for asking.
大家还好吗  发生了什么
Is everyone okay? What happened?
斯库鲁伏击
Skrull ambush.
我以为我们失去你了
I thought we'd lost you.
你找到索拉了吗
Did you find Soh-Larr?
那根本不是索拉
It wasn't Soh-Larr.
是塔罗斯模仿了他  连他的密码都知道
Talos simmed him. Even knew his code.
那不可能
That's impossible.
那密码是在他的潜意识里的
That code was buried in his unconscious.
斯库鲁人动了我的大脑
The Skrulls messed with my mind.
他们用的那台机器
The machine that they used...
我觉得他们就是那样得知了索拉的密码
I think it's how they extracted Soh-Larr's code.
弗斯  你在哪
Vers, where are you?
我在C53星球上
I'm on planet C-53.
斯库鲁在找一个叫劳森的人
The Skrulls are looking for someone named Lawson.
谁
Who?
她是我看到的人
She's who I see.
她什么
She's what?
弗斯
Vers?
弗斯  什么
Vers, what?
她是个科学家
She's a scientist.
他们觉得她研发出了光速科技
They think that she's cracked the code on light-speed tech.
我得赶在他们之前找到她
I have to get to her before they do...
否则他们就能入侵新星系了
or else they'll be able to invade new galaxies.
不  你已经被抓到一次了
No. You've been caught once already.
C53离我们多远
How far is C-53?
离最近的跳跃点有22小时的路程
Closest jump point is 22 hours.
弗斯  原地别动  等我们赶到
Vers, hold your position until we get there.
保持通讯器在线  以便我们联系你
Keep your comms online so we can contact you.
不  如果他们先于我找到...
No! What if they get a hold of it before...
很抱歉
We're sorry.
您拨打的号码需要输入
A long-distance company access code
-长途电话公司  -勇
- is required for the number - Yon?
-接入码  -弗斯
- you have dialed. - Vers?
-弗斯  -请用接入码
- Vers? - Please dial your call
拨打电话
with the access code.
弗斯
Vers?
如果斯库鲁人控制了她的心智
If the Skrulls got to her,
她就不能被信任了
she's compromised.
她比你想的要坚强
She's stronger than you think.
去过C53吗
Ever been to C-53?
去过一次
Once.
破地方
It's a real shithole.
新人  去跟那个保安谈谈
Rookie! Go talk to the rent-a-cop.
是你上报的吗
Did you call this in?
信标激活
Beacon activated.
打扰  小姐
Excuse me, miss.
你知道有位女士把那边的
You know anything about a lady blowing a hole
百视达屋顶轰了个洞吗
through the roof of that Blockbuster over there?
证人说她穿了一身激光枪战的衣服
Witness says she was dressed for laser tag.
嗯  我觉得她去那边了
Yeah, I think she went that way.
我想问你些问题
I'd like to ask you some questions.
或许教教你怎么用深夜投件箱
Maybe give you the 411 on the late-night drop box.
可以出示身份证吗
Could I see some identification, please?
弗斯  克里星际战队
Vers. Kree Starforce.
我们不把身份证明写在小纸片上
We don't carry our identification on little cards.
弗斯
Vers?
星际战队
Starforce?
你打算在这里待多久
How long you plan to be in town?
等我找到
I'll be out of your hair...
正在潜入你们星球的斯库鲁人
as soon as I track down the Skrulls
我就会离开了
that are infiltrating your planet.
斯库鲁人
Skrulls?
变形者
Shapeshifters?
他们能变形成任何生命形式  连DNA也能复制
They can transform into any life-form down to the DNA.
天呐  你们完全不知道  是吧
Oh, boy. You guys don't have any clue, do you?
等等
Hold on.
我们怎么知道你不是那种变形者
How do we know you're not one of those shapeshifters?
恭喜  弗瑞特工
Congratulations, Agent Fury.
你总算问了个有用的问题
You have finally asked a relevant question.
不  恭喜你  星际战队女士
No! Congratulations to you, Starforce lady.
你被捕了
You're under arrest.
新人
Rook!
新人  我们走
Rook, let's roll!
你看到她的武器了吗
Did you see her weapon?
没有
I did not.
看路啊
Watch it!
嫌疑人在北行列车上  正在追赶
Suspect on northbound train. In pursuit.
"相信我  真正的信徒"  "相信我"
"Trust me, true believer." "Trust me."
耍酷一族
"相信我  真正的信徒"
"Trust me, true believer."
放开
Get off!
列车前面要进隧道了
Train's heading for a tunnel up ahead.
我们去车站接他们
Let's greet them at the station.
弗瑞先生  这里是科尔森特工
Mr. Fury, this is Agent Coulson.
我还在百视达呢
I'm still here at the Blockbuster. And, uh,
大家都哪去了
where'd everybody go?
我已经完成证据收集了
I finished collecting evidence...
快叫救护车
We need an ambulance!
谁打下911
Someone call 911!
神盾局官方行动  别过来
Official S.H.I.E.L.D. activity. Stay back.
温迪·劳森博士  飞马计划
潘乔酒吧
加州  罗莎蒙德
该设备已断网或被占用
潜水衣挺酷
Nice scuba suit.
幽默点嘛  亲爱的
Lighten up, honey, huh?
能给我笑笑吗
Got a smile for me?
怪胎
Freak.
所有地球上的生命都是碳基的  但他不是
All life on Earth is carbon-based. Not this guy.
不管他是什么做的
Whatever he runs on,
反正周期表上没有
it's not on the periodic table.
你是说  他不是这里的
You're saying he's not from around here?
你的眼睛怎么样了
How's your eye?
眼睛倒没事
Well, I'd say fine...
就是不敢相信我看到的东西
but it can't believe what it's seeing.
你说这玩意之前是科尔森的样子
You say this thing looked like Coulson?
说话也像
Talked like him, too.
那女人说还有更多这种人
And the woman said that there were more?
她说的是"潜入"
The word she used was "infiltration."
你相信她吗
You believe her?
直到见到这个才信
Not till I saw this.
你有什么打算
What's your plan?
我能找到那个百视达姑娘
I'll find Blockbuster girl.
有桩摩托车盗窃的报案
I got word on a motorcycle thief
女贼符合她的描述
that fits her description.
如果她能说出这些蜥蜴人为什么来
If she can tell us why these lizards are here...
或许她也能告诉我们怎么赶走他们
maybe she can tell us how to kick 'em to the curb.
好
Good.
但你自己行动  我们谁都不能信任
Do it alone, though. We can't trust anyone.
连我们自己人都不行
Not even our own men.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
他们可真丑  是吧
They're ugly bastards, aren't they?
是啊  可不比布拉德·皮特  长官
Yeah, well, he's no Brad Pitt, sir.
安然超度吧  我的朋友
Safe journey to the beyond, my friend.
我会完成我们的大业
I will finish what we started.
最好别靠太近  老大
I wouldn't get too close there, boss.
任何人不得进出
No one in or out.
需要点什么
What can I get ya?
这张照片是哪拍的
Where was this photograph taken?
一个机场
An airport.
飞马计划在哪
Where's Pegasus?
那是机密
That's classified.
我给你建立的档案也是
Not unlike the file I started on you.
但看来你还换装了
But I see you've changed it up a bit since then.
垃圾摇滚挺衬你
Grunge is a good look for you.
你今天不顺吗  弗瑞特工
Did you have a rough day, Agent Fury?
还行吧
It was cool, you know?
遭遇了太空入侵  大型追车
Had a space invasion, big car chase.
还看了一场外星人尸检
Got to watch an alien autopsy.
也就典型的工作日
Typical nine-to-five.
你看到一个了
So you saw one?
我并不怎么信外星人
I was never one to believe in aliens...
但那画面我是忘不掉了
but I can't unsee that.
这会比较尴尬  但我必须问
This is gonna get a little awkward, but I gotta ask.
你觉得我也是那种绿玩意
You think I'm one of those green things.
小心驶得万年船
Can't be too careful.
我可是百分百的红血地球人
You are looking at 100% red-blooded Earth man.
我恐怕需要点证明
I'm afraid I'm gonna need proof.
你是想验唾液还是验尿
We talking cheek swab or urine sample?
不  DNA也会一样的
No. The DNA would match.
那我的美国在线密码呢
Want my AOL password?
斯库鲁人只能模仿宿主的近期记忆
Skrulls can only sim recent memories of their host bodies.
你想聊私事
You wanna get personal.
-你出生在哪  -阿拉巴马亨茨维尔
- Where were you born? - Huntsville, Alabama.
但严格讲  我并不记得那些岁月了
But technically, I don't remember that part.
-第一只宠物的名字  -探探先生
- Name of your first pet? - Mr. Snoofers.
-探探先生  -我就这么说的
- Mr. Snoofers? - That's what I said.
我通过了吗
Do I pass?
还没  第一份工作
Not yet. First job?
士兵  高中毕业就参军了
Soldier. Straight out of high school.
退役时已做到了上校
Left the ranks a full bird colonel.
-然后呢  -间谍
- Then? - Spy.
-在哪做  -那时是冷战
- Where? - It was the Cold War.
我们无所不在
We were everywhere.
贝尔法斯特  布加勒斯特
Belfast. Bucharest.
贝尔格莱德  布达佩斯
Belgrade. Budapest.
我喜欢B开头的  比较押韵
I like the B's. I can make them rhyme.
-现在呢  -干六年文职了
- Now? - Been riding a desk for the past six years...
想搞清楚我们未来的敌人会从哪来
trying to figure out where our future enemies are coming from.
真没想到
Never occurred to me
会是从天上来
they would be coming from above.
说出一个非常怪异
Name a detail so bizarre
斯库鲁人绝编造不出来的细节
a Skrull could never fabricate it.
如果一片吐司被对角切开  我就不能吃了
If toast is cut diagonally, I can't eat it.
你并不需要知道那个  是吧
You didn't need that, did you?
是啊  不  但我喜欢
No. No, I didn't. But I enjoyed it.
好吧  该你了
Okay. Your turn.
证明你不是斯库鲁人
Prove you're not a Skrull.
这怎么就能向我证明
And how is that supposed to prove to me
你不是斯库鲁人了
you're not a Skrull?
那是光子炮
That's a photon blast.
怎么
And?
斯库鲁人做不到的
A Skrull can't do that.
那么  上校
So, a full bird colonel
改做间谍  改做神盾局特工
turned spy turned S.H.I.E.L.D. agent...
你的安全权限肯定挺高
must have pretty high security clearance.
飞马计划在哪
Where's Pegasus?
好吧  斯库鲁人能模仿外星种族
Okay. The Skrulls sim alien races
以潜入并夺取星球
to infiltrate and take over planets.
你是个克里人  你们是高尚的战士种族
And you're a Kree? A race of noble warriors?
英雄  高尚的战士英雄
Heroes. Noble warrior heroes.
那么  斯库鲁人找劳森博士做什么
So, um, what do Skrulls want with Dr. Lawson?
他们认为她在飞马计划
They believe that she developed
开发了一种光速引擎
a light-speed engine at Pegasus.
光速引擎
Light-speed engine?
得承认  这还不算我今天听到的最疯狂的事
Gotta admit, that's not the craziest thing I've heard today.
这还早嘛
Well, it's still early.
你呢  你想要什么
And you, what do you want?
及时阻止斯库鲁人
To stop the Skrulls before they become unstoppable.
然后呢
And?
战争是一种通用语言
Look, war is a universal language.
我能辨认得出一个擅自行动的士兵
I know a rogue soldier when I see one.
你有私人的动机
You got a personal stake in this.
这里是政府地界
This is government property.
请调头
Turn your vehicle around.
尼古拉斯·约瑟夫·弗瑞  神盾局特工
Nicholas Joseph Fury. Agent of S.H.I.E.L.D.
请把拇指按在面板上
Place your thumb on the pad.
稍等
One moment.
尼古拉斯·约瑟夫·弗瑞  你有三个名字
Nicholas Joseph Fury. You have three names?
大家都喊我弗瑞
Everybody calls me Fury.
不是尼古拉斯  或约瑟夫  或尼克
Not Nicholas. Not Joseph. Not Nick.
就叫弗瑞
Just Fury.
-你妈妈怎么喊你  -弗瑞
- What does your mom call you? - Fury.
-你怎么喊她  -弗瑞
- What do you call her? - Fury.
你的孩子呢
What about your kids?
如果我有了孩子  他们也会喊我弗瑞
If I have them, they'll call me Fury.
你们可以进入了
You are cleared for access.
谢谢
Thank you.
飞马计划
太空总署美国空军联合基地
等等
Hold up.
你看上去像谁的叛逆侄女
You look like somebody's disaffected niece.
戴上这个
Put that on.
-这是什么  -是神盾局的标志
- What is it? - It's the S.H.I.E.L.D. Logo.
在衣服上标注你的身份
Does, uh, announcing your identity on clothing
有助于你工作的秘密性吗
help with the covert part of your job?
穿橡胶衣的太空战士还好意思说我
Said the space soldier who was wearing a rubber suit.
把法兰绒衬衫脱了
Lose the flannel.
有什么事吗
How can I help you?
我们是神盾局特工
We're agents of S.H.I.E.L.D.
神盾局  三级
我们在找一个叫劳森的女人
We're looking for a woman named Lawson.
温迪·劳森博士
A Dr. Wendy Lawson.
你认识她吗
Do you know her?
跟我来
Follow me.
你知道什么叫"迎宾队"吗
You familiar with the phrase "welcome wagon"?
不
No.
反正不是这样的
Well, this ain't it.
那是个通讯器吗
Is that a communicator?
是的  最先进的双向寻呼机
Yeah. State-of-the-art two-way pager.
你在呼叫谁
Who are you paging?
我妈  别担心  我没提你
My mom. Don't worry. I didn't mention you.
在目标地点遭到扣押  需要支援
地下五层  档案馆
你先请
After you.
厉害
Impressive.
你该看看我能用回形针施展什么魔法
You should see what I can do with a paperclip.
小家伙  你好吗
Hey, there. How are you?
天呐  看看你  看看你啊
Oh, my goodness. Look at you. Just look at you.
你是不是最可爱了
Aren't you the cutest little thing?
你多可爱  你叫什么
Aren't you cute? And what's your name, huh?
你叫什么
What's your name?
"咕咕"  酷猫酷名
"Goose." Cool name for a cool cat.
弗瑞
Fury?
我就回来
I'll be back.
档案馆
等我把指纹拿出来
Let me get my fingerprint out.
把它打开就行
Just let me unravel this puppy.
你就坐在那里  看着我摆弄胶带
You sat there and watched me play with tape?
你只需要...
When all you had to do was...
我不想抢你的风头
I didn't wanna steal your thunder.
劳森
Lawson.
劳森的光速引擎图纸
Lawson's plan for the light-speed engine.
项目中止
他们为什么中止了这个项目呢
I wonder why they terminated the project.
或许是因为她
Maybe because she's
疯了
cuckoo.
克里文字
Kree glyphs?
劳森不是疯子
Lawson is not cuckoo.
她是克里人
She's Kree.
反正她死了
Well, she's dead.
什么
What?
她在一次未授权试飞中
She crashed the Asis aircraft
撞毁了一架艾西斯战机
doing an unauthorized test flight.
还害死了个飞行员
Took a pilot down with her.
所以这里的保安才那么不友好
That's why security here is so unfriendly.
他们在掩盖一个价值十亿的过失
They're covering up a billion-dollar mistake.
你的光速引擎也烧毁了
And your light-speed engine is toast.
坠机什么时候发生的
When did this crash happen?
六年前  1989年
Six years ago. 1989.
飞行员是谁
Who was the pilot?
大部分文件都编辑过了
Most of this thing's redacted...
但这里有一份玛利亚·兰博的证词
but there is a testimonial here from a Maria Rambeau.
她是最后见到活着的她们的人
Last person to see them alive.
信息收到  凯勒
你没事吧
You okay?
马上回来
Back in a minute.
这不是为了作战
This isn't about fighting wars.
而是为了结束战争
It's about ending them.
我知道劳森是克里人
I know Lawson was Kree.
她就在C53星球上  而且死于坠机
She was here on C-53 and died in a plane crash.
你对此知情吗
Do you know anything about this?
我刚发现了一份C53发来的任务报告
I just discovered a mission report sent from C-53.
我有权告诉你的不多  弗斯  但是
There's only so much I'm cleared to tell you, Vers, but...
劳森是一名卧底克里特工  名叫玛威尔
Lawson was an undercover Kree operative named Mar-Vell.
她在研究一种独特的能量核
She was working on a unique energy core.
实验一种据说可以
Experimenting with tech that apparently
助我们赢下战争的科技
could help us win the war.
她还在吗
She still here?
她在配合调查  长官
She's cooperating with the investigation, sir.
-你们留下  -是  长官
- You men stay here. - Yes, sir.
我要单独审讯她
I want to question her alone.
干得漂亮  尼古拉斯
Excellent work, Nicholas.
上面提到我了吗
Does it say anything about me?
提到你  当然没有
Anything about you? No, of course not.
怎么会呢
Why would it?
我找到证据  表明我曾在这里生活
I found evidence that I had a life here.
在C53上吗
On C-53?
我去见至高智慧时  看到的就是玛威尔
Mar-Vell is who I see when I visit the Supreme Intelligence.
我认识她  我认识身为劳森的她
I knew her. And I knew her as Lawson.
这更像是斯库鲁人的模仿  弗斯
This sounds like Skrull simulation, Vers.
不  不是  因为我记得  我来过这里
No, it's not. Because I remember. I was here.
停下  记住你的训练
Stop. Remember your training.
了解你的敌人  你也可能是你的敌人
Know your enemy. It could be you.
别被情绪影响了你的判断力
Do not let your emotions override your judgment.
她在地下六层
She's on sublevel six.
我在五层下
I'll get off on five...
走楼梯  以防她企图逃跑
and take the stairs in case she makes a run for it.
像我们在哈瓦那时那样  两面夹击
Do a pincer move like we did in Havana.
对
Right.
就像在哈瓦那时那样
Like we did in Havana.
我们快到跳跃点了
We're nearing the jump point.
别关信标  让我们能找到你
Leave your beacon on so I can find you.
我们会查清真相的  弗斯
We'll get to the bottom of this, Vers.
我们一起
Together.
好
Okay.
弗斯
Vers!
弗瑞在与目标串通
Fury's colluding with the target.
那他为什么要叫支援
Then why would he call us in?
我只知道他也要抓
All I know is we take him in, too.
不论死活
Dead or alive.
Dead or alive?
上上
Go. Go, go!
是我说错了什么吗
Was it something I said?
其实  我并不需要这个也能看见
Now, you know, I don't really need these to see...
但这身打扮少不了它
but they do kinda complete the look.
是不是
Don't you think?
你叫他们来的
You called them in?
我不好
My bad.
科尔森  你发现他们了吗
Coulson, do you have eyes on them?
他们不在下面
They're not down here.
我们上楼吧
Let's try up there.
-什么  -你的通讯器
- What? - Your communicator.
在你手里显然不安全
You obviously can't be trusted with it.
你会飞这玩意吗
Do you know how to fly this thing?
试试便知
We'll see.
回答会不会就行了
That's a yes or no question.
会
Yes.
这就对了
That's what I'm talking about!
我们有个偷渡者
We got a stowaway.
撑住  咕咕
Hang on, Goose.
咕咕
Goose.
不  咕咕
No, Goose.
谁是只乖喵喵
Who's a good kitty, huh?
咕咕
Goose?
没错
Yes, that's right.
谁是只乖喵喵  咕咕
Who's a good kitty, Goose?
你是只乖喵喵
You the good kitty, that's right.
看到认识的人了吗
See anyone you know?
说来好笑
Funny story.
我奄奄一息地被送到哈拉  失去了记忆
I arrived on Hala near dead. No memory.
那是六年前的事
That was six years ago.
所以你觉得你是那个
So, you think you're the pilot
跟劳森博士一起坠机的飞行员
that went down with Dr. Lawson?
我是说  最后见到活着的她们的人
I'm saying the last person to see them alive
或许能告诉我们
could probably tell us.
玛利亚·兰博
Maria Rambeau?
我们怎么去路易斯安那州
So, how do we get to Louisiana?
往东飞  在孟菲斯右转
Due east. Hang a right at Memphis.
那个特工
That agent...
阻止了斯库鲁人找到我们的那个
that stopped the Skrulls from finding us?
科尔森  新来的
Coulson. The new guy.
看来他还不恨我
I guess he doesn't hate me yet.
是啊  给他时间吧
Yeah, well, give him time.
看来他是有种感觉
I guess he had a feeling, you know?
于是听从了直觉  而违抗命令
Went with his gut against orders.
这是很难做到的
That's a really hard thing to do.
但也是我们的人性
But it's what keeps us human.
我经常为此惹麻烦呢
I get in trouble for that. A lot.
这我看出来了
I can see that about you.
营救把你出卖给斯库鲁人的家伙
Rescuing the guy who sold you out to the Skrulls?
那不是标准的克里人行动规章吧
I'm guessing that's not standard Kree operating procedure.
如果你不向我上级打小报告  那我也不说
Well, I won't tell your boss if you don't tell mine.
罗南
Ronan.
指控者已完成了行动
The Accusers completed their operation...
但因为你们小队  更重要的任务失败了
but the greater mission was a failure, thanks to your team.
那是个陷阱
It was a trap
是为引诱我们的特工弗斯到托法  好绑架她
to lure our operative Vers to Torfa and kidnap her.
告诉我们地点
Give us their location.
我们会解决恐怖分子威胁
We'll take care of the terrorist threat.
你要把他们炸出银河系吗
By bombing them out of the galaxy?
不  我们来解决
No, we'll handle this.
不论在哪  一小撮斯库鲁人
A cell of Skrulls anywhere
对所有克里人都是威胁
is a threat to Kree everywhere.
他们在哪
Where are they?
-他们...  -不见了
- They are... - Lost.
暂时下落不明
They are lost for now.
但我们会找到他们的
But we will find them.
那去吧
Do so,
否则我们就接手
or we will.
继续航向C53
Maintain the course for C-53.
打扰  我找玛利亚·兰博
Excuse me, I'm looking for Maria Rambeau.
卡罗尔阿姨
Auntie Carol?
妈妈  是卡罗尔阿姨
Mom, it's Auntie Carol!
我就知道  大家都说你死了
I knew it! Everyone said you were dead!
但我们知道他们说谎了
But we knew they were lying.
我不是你以为的那个人
I'm not really who you think I am.
这是我听过的最疯狂的故事了
That is the craziest shit I ever heard.
会变形的绿外星人  没有这种事
Green transforming aliens? There's no such thing.
你说得太对了  小姑娘
You are absolutely right, young lady.
是没有这种事
There is no such thing.
因为即便有
'Cause if there were,
我们也不会想说出去
we would want to keep that to ourselves.
你不信吗
You don't believe me?
不会吧
No way!
好酷啊
That's so cool!
她的手可不止能泡茶呢
She can do a lot more than make tea with those hands.
比如呢  露两手
Like what? Show us.
待会儿的吧
Maybe later.
你的东西我都还留着呢
I kept all your stuff.
我去拿
I'll go get it.
你要去帮帮她吗
You want to give her a hand with that?
你什么都不记得了
You don't remember anything?
我会看到些片段
I see flashes.
一些时刻
Little moments.
但我不知道那是不是真的
But I can't tell what's real.
如果我可以把那天早上发生的事拼凑起来
If I could just piece together what happened that morning...
或许就都能说得通了
maybe it'll all make sense.
你破晓时猛敲我的门  把我吵醒了
You woke me up banging on my door at dawn.
你总这样
Your usual move.
当时  我们必须起得很早
Back then, we had to get up so early.
空军还是不许女性飞战斗任务
The Air Force still wasn't letting women fly combat...
所以  为劳森测试飞机是我们
so testing Lawson's planes was our only shot
唯一能做点要紧事的机会
at doing something that mattered.
你想开你的老野马飙车去基地
You wanted to race to base in your old Mustang...
我并不想跟你争
and I wasn't about to argue,
因为我知道我的科迈罗稳赢不输
'cause I knew my Camaro would dominate.
但你作弊了  走了捷径
But you cheated, took a shortcut.
捷径怎么就算作弊了
Since when is a shortcut cheating?
因为那有违预定的交战规则
Since it violates the predetermined rules of engagement.
这我可绝对不记得
I definitely don't remember those.
当然了
Of course you don't.
我到机库时  劳森很焦躁
When I got to the hangar, Lawson was agitated.
她说她还要拯救生命
She said she had lives to save.
她想自己开艾西斯
She was trying to take the Asis up herself,
但你说...
but you said that...
如果事关人命  那我要来开
If there were lives at stake, I would fly the plane.
对
Yeah.
Yep.
重大的英雄时刻
Big hero moment.
那种我们都一直在等待的时刻
The kind of moment we'd both been waiting for.
博士一向很特别
The doc was always unique.
所以我们喜欢她
That's why we liked her.
但现在你说她是另一个星球来的
But now you're saying she's from another planet.
我知道你肯定很难接受
I know this must be hard for you.
怎么  这部分吗
Oh, what? This part right here?
不  不
No. No.
难的部分是失去我最好的朋友
What's hard is losing my best friend...
但这任务太机密
in a mission so secret
他们就假装什么都没发生
they act like it never even happened.
难的部分是知道你一直都活在某处
Hard is knowing you were out there somewhere
固执地不肯死去
too damn stubborn to die.
现在时隔六年  你又跑来
And now you come up in here after six years...
双手能发射高能
with your supercharged fire hands...
还要我喊你
and you expect me to call you...
什么...弗斯吗
I don't even know what. Vers?
你现在真是这个人了吗
Is that really who you are now?
我不知道
I don't know.
来看看
Come look!
这是我们在万圣节时
This is me and you on Halloween.
著名女飞行员
我是阿梅莉亚·埃尔哈特
I'm Amelia Earhart
摇滚女星
你是詹尼斯·乔普林
and you're Janis Joplin.
这是你小时候
This is you when you were little.
你跟你父母关系不好
You didn't get along with your parents...
所以妈妈说  我们成了你真正的家人
so Mom said we became your real family.
这是我们圣诞节的时候
This is us on Christmas.
我收到了我最喜欢的兔子拖鞋
I got my favorite bunny slippers.
这也是张你小时候的照片
This is another picture of you when you were little.
你一直想当飞行员
You've always wanted to be a pilot.
这是你刚毕业时
And this is right after you graduated.
这是你圣诞节时收到的狗狗
This was your dog that you got for Christmas...
这是你空军小队的大合照
This is a picture of everybody from your Air Force team.
这是你和妈妈在一天训练顺利完成后照的
And this is you with Mom right after a good day of training.
他们是三个你最喜欢的人
These were your three favorite guys.
等等  我忘了
Wait. I forgot.
你的外套
Your jacket.
我在上面洒了番茄酱
Mom doesn't let me wear it anymore
妈妈就不许我穿了
after I spilled ketchup on it.
卡罗尔·丹
那是坠机时唯一留下的
That was all that survived the crash.
至少我们以为是
Or so we thought.
别去开门
Don't answer that.
只是我的邻居
It's just my neighbor.
他们能变形成任何人
They can change into anyone.
你好
Hi there.
有什么事
What do you want?
汤姆
Tom.
这是我朋友  卡罗尔
This is my friend, Carol.
认识你很高兴
Pleased to meet you.
老天爷
Yowzers.
这里的静电可真要命
Static electricity out here's no joke.
我注意到你停在路边的那架大鸟
I noticed that peculiar bird you got parked by the road...
我只是想问
and I was just wondering...
我能不能带孩子们过来
if you mind if I bring the boys over
仔细看看
to get a closer look-see?
-仔细看看  -是啊
- A closer look-see? - Yeah.
看停在路边的大鸟
To see the "bird" parked out by the road?
你装得还真像啊  是吧
You're really working overtime to sell this one, aren't you,
塔罗斯
Talos?
抱歉  汤姆  现在真的不太方便
I'm sorry, Tom. This really isn't a good time.
我明天再去找你  好吗
I'll come by tomorrow, okay?
好了
Okay.
你该对邻居更客气点的
You know, you really should be kinder to your neighbors.
说不定哪天还要去借糖呢
You never know when you're gonna need to borrow some sugar.
等一下
Now, hang on a second.
先别急着挥你的魔术手
Before you go swinging those jazz hands around...
把你朋友家砸得稀巴烂
making a mess of your friend's house...
而且你家很漂亮  女士
It's a lovely home, miss.
天呐
Oh, my God!
怎么回事
What the hell?
没人会伤害她的
No one's gonna hurt the girl.
别杀我
Just don't kill me.
那样情况就真的麻烦了
That would really complicate the situation.
我再过五秒就要麻烦一墙的
I'm about five seconds from complicating that wall
恶心斯库鲁脑浆了
with some ugly-ass Skrull brains.
抱歉我模仿了你的上司
I'm sorry I simmed your boss.
但现在  我以真身站在你们面前
But now I stand before you as my true self.
没有欺骗
Without deception.
那外面的是谁
And who is that out there?
好吧  有道理
Okay, that's a fair point...
但我相信你能理解
but I'm sure that you understand
我必须采取些预防措施
I had to take some precautions.
我看到你碾压了我20个最好的手下
I saw you crush 20 of my best men
而且你的手还被困着
with your hands bound.
我只想谈谈
I just wanna talk.
上次我们谈时
Last time we talked,
我被倒吊了起来
I ended up hanging from my ankles.
那时我还不知道你的身份
That was before I knew who you were.
我还不知道你跟其他人的不同之处
Before I knew what made you different from the others.
我有段飞马计划的录音
I have an audio recording from Pegasus...
录的是六年前一场坠机中
of your voice from a plane crash
你的声音
six years ago...
那个设备好像被你们称为"黑匣子"
on a device I believe you call a "black box."
他们说黑匣子毁于了坠机
They told me it was destroyed in the crash.
你怎么拿到的
How'd you get it?
她不懂
She don't understand.
小姑娘  我有独特的技能  让我可以
Young lady, I have a special skill that kind of allows me to
进入我不该进的地方
get into places I'm not supposed to be.
你再敢喊我"小姑娘"
Call me "young lady" again...
我就一脚踢到我不该踢到的地方
I'm gonna put my foot in a place it's not supposed to be.
难道要我猜那是哪里吗
Am I supposed to guess where that is?
你的屁股
Your ass.
好吧  我懂  我们都有点紧张
Okay, I get it. We're all a little on edge here.
但听着  我只需要你帮我
But, look, I just need your help
解码一个坐标
decoding some coordinates.
如果你坐下  听听录音
If you'll sit down and you'll listen to this...
我保证  你不会失望的
I assure you, it'll be worth your while.
把你的朋友叫进来  我就听
Call your buddy back inside and I'll listen.
好
Deal.
天呐  把那玩意拿远点
Oh, my God! Get that thing away.
它怎么进来的
How'd that get in here?
猫吗
The cat?
你不会怕这个吧
This isn't what you're afraid of, is it?
那不是猫
That's not a cat.
-那是噬元兽  -噬元兽
- That's a Flerken. - A Flerken?
妈妈
Mom?
莫妮卡
Monica.
我为什么不能听
Why can't I listen, too?
怎么回事
What's happening?
在加载
It's loading.
输入坐标
Punch in the coordinates
5229  负47  8.768  0.2
5-2-2-9, negative 4-7, 8.7-6-8, 0.2.
收到  我们去哪  博士
Copy that. Where are we going, Doc?
我的实验室
My laboratory.
你的实验室  什么意思
Your laboratory? What do you mean?
不
Oh, no.
那是  等等  那是什么
Is that... Wait, what is that?
我的雷达上没有显示
It's not showing up on my radar.
快走  卡罗尔  快飞
Go, Carol. Fly!
那可不是米格  劳森  他们是什么人
That's no MiG, Lawson. Who the hell are they?
那是坏人  飞快点
Those are the bad guys. Fly faster now!
是  长官
Yes, ma'am.
-他们想要什么  -我  我的研究
- What do they want? - Me. My work.
我就不该带你来
I never should have brought you along.
要难受了
Here come some G's.
他们在向后开火  撑住
They're firing backwards. Hold on!
跳伞  跳伞
Bail out! Bail out! Bail out!
撑住  劳森
Stay with me, Lawson!
卡罗尔  回复  你收到吗
Carol, come in. Do you copy?
我收到  我们坠机了
Yeah, I copy. We hit ground.
卡罗尔  你没事吧  你收到吗
Carol, are you okay? Do you copy?
我收到
Yeah! I copy.
博士
Doc?
你的血
Your blood.
是蓝的
It's blue.
是啊  但我的发型没事吧
Yeah, but, uh, how's my hair?
帮帮我  好吗
Help me out, will ya?
我得在他们赶到前毁掉它
I gotta destroy it before they get here.
劳森
Lawson?
记得我怎么说我们的工作的吗
You remember what I said about our work here?
目的是什么
What it's for?
结束战争
To end wars?
对  但战争的规模比你想的要大
Yeah. But the wars are bigger than you know.
该死
Damn it!
我不叫劳森
My name is not Lawson.
我的真名是玛威尔
My real name is Mar-Vell,
我来自哈拉星球
and I come from a planet called Hala.
我想说你是脑袋糊涂了
I would say that you're delusional... but
但我们刚被太空飞船打下来
we just got shot down by a spaceship
你的血又是蓝的
and your blood is blue.
听着  我半辈子都在打一场可耻的战争
Listen, I spent half my life fighting a shameful war.
你快走吧  别让我更加懊悔了
Now, skedaddle before you give me any more regrets.
记住那坐标  好吗
Just remember the coordinates, okay?
你得单独救他们了
You gotta save 'em without me.
救谁  怎么救
Save who? How?
我得在他们找到前炸毁引擎
Now I gotta blow this engine before they find it.
你干什么
What are you doing?
我们无意伤害你
We have no interest in hurting you.
是吗
No?
因为你们猛烈的火力让我不那么觉得
'Cause all the shooting kinda gave me the wrong impression!
能量核
The energy core.
在哪
Where is it?
伞兵救援很快就到
Pararescue's on the way.
还有两分钟  你就会被包围
You have two minutes until you're surrounded.
那就没必要继续跟你废话了
Then I see no reason to prolong this conversation.
不  等等
No, wait!
你是问那个能量核吗
You mean that energy core?
不
No!
指挥官  她还在动  可以开火吗
Commander? She's still moving. Permission to fire.
别开火
Hold your fire.
什么都不剩了
There's nothing left.
核被摧毁了
The core has been destroyed.
弗斯
她吸收了核的能量
She absorbed its power.
她要跟我们走
She's coming with us.
他骗了我
He lied to me.
我所知的一切都是谎言
Everything that I knew was a lie.
现在你明白了
Now, you understand.
什么  我明白什么了
What? What do I understand now?
勇·罗格杀了玛威尔
Yon-Rogg killed Mar-Vell.
他杀了她
He killed her...
因为她发现
'cause she found out that
自己站在战争中不正义的一方
she was on the wrong side of an unjust war.
不
No.
斯库鲁人都是恐怖分子
Your people are terrorists.
他们杀无辜者
They kill innocents.
我看到托法上的废墟了
I saw the ruins on Torfa.
那是指控者干的
Ruins that the Accusers are responsible for.
我们是作为难民在托法上生活
My people lived as refugees on Torfa.
无家可归  就因为我们反对克里统治
Homeless, ever since we resisted Kree rule...
被他们摧毁了家园
and they destroyed our planet.
我们仅剩的不多的人
And the handful of us that are left
也会遭到屠戮
will be slaughtered next...
除非你帮我完成玛威尔的目标
unless you help me finish what Mar-Vell started.
她发现的核
The core that she found
能驱动光速飞船
would have powered a light-speed ship...
可以带我们前往安全之处
capable of carrying us to safety.
前往克里人找不到的新家园
A new home where the Kree can't reach us.
劳森总说我们飞马计划的工作
Lawson always told us that our work at Pegasus
不是为了作战
wasn't to fight wars...
是为了结束战争
but to end them.
她希望你帮我们找到能量核
She wanted you to help us find the core.
我已经摧毁了它
Well, I already destroyed it.
不  你毁掉了引擎
No, you destroyed the engine.
但驱动它的能量核在其他地方
The core that powered it is in a remote location.
如果你能帮我们解码坐标
If you help us decode those coordinates...
我们就能找到它
we can find it.
你会用它对付我们的
You'll use it to destroy us.
我们只想要个家
We just want a home.
你和我都因克里人失去了一切
You and I lost everything at the hands of the Kree.
你还不明白吗
Can't you see it now?
你不是他们的人
You're not one of them.
你不了解我
You don't know me.
你不知道我是谁
You have no idea who I am.
我都不知道我是谁
I don't even know who I am!
你是卡罗尔·丹弗斯
You are Carol Danvers.
你是那个黑匣子上录下的女人
You are the woman on that black box
为了做正确的事不惜冒生命危险
risking her life to do the right thing.
我最好的朋友
My best friend...
在我没有其他人时  支持我这个单亲妈妈
who supported me as a mother and a pilot
和飞行员
when no one else did.
你聪明  幽默  非常烦人
You are smart, and funny, and a huge pain in the ass...
你是我认识的最强大的人
and you were the most powerful person I knew...
哪怕是你还不会用手开火的时候
way before you could shoot fire from your fists.
你听到了吗
You hear me?
Do you hear me?
过来  过来  姑娘
Come here. Come here, girl.
有我呢
I got you.
我知道我不配让你信任我
I know I don't deserve your trust...
但你是我们唯一的线索
but you were our only lead.
我们发现你的能量信号
We discovered that your energy signature
与玛威尔的能量核一致
matched Mar-Vell's core.
现在我们知道原因了
Now we know why.
如果你知道它对我是多么重要
If only you knew the importance of it to me.
我就需要你帮我
I just need your help
破解玛威尔实验室的坐标
decoding the coordinates to Mar-Vell's lab.
那不是坐标  是状态向量
Those weren't coordinates. They're state vectors.
环绕位置和速度的
For orbital position and velocity.
你在地球上找不到她的实验室
You didn't find her lab on Earth,
因为它不在地球上
'cause it's not on Earth.
那是六年前坠机日时的地点
That was the location on the date of the crash six years ago.
只要追踪其轨迹
If we track its course,
马上就能在环绕轨道上找到它
we'll find it in orbit right now.
只是基本物理
It's just basic physics.
轨道环绕
In orbit?
就那么难破解吗
Was that so difficult to figure out?
你可是我的科技人员
I mean, you're my science guy, right?
勇·罗格很快就会找到我
Yon-Rogg will catch up to me soon.
我们得在他之前找到能量核
We've got to get to the core before he does.
我们上太空吗
We're going to space?
乘什么去
In what?
稍稍调整下你的飞机应该就行
A few tweaks to your vessel should do it.
我可以负责改装
I can handle the modifications.
你的科技人员
Your science guy.
我需要个副驾
Well, I could use a copilot.
不  我不能
No. No, I can't.
我不能丢下莫妮卡
I can't leave Monica.
妈妈  没事  我可以去外婆外公家住
Mom, it's okay. I can stay with Gramma and Paw-paw.
我不能去  宝贝  太危险了
There's no way I'm going, baby. It's too dangerous.
测试新航空科技还危险呢
Testing brand-new aerospace tech is dangerous...
你以前不也做那个吗
and you used to do that.
你的计划是乘坐一架
Your plan is to leave the atmosphere
原本不能离开大气的飞机离开大气
in a craft not designed for the journey...
而且还可能遭遇
and you anticipate hostile encounters
科技更先进的外星敌人
with a technologically-superior foreign enemy.
是吗
Correct?
所以我说啊
That's what I'm saying.
-你必须去  -莫妮卡
- You have to go! - Monica!
你有机会去执行任务史上
You have a chance to fly the coolest mission
最酷的任务
in the history of missions...
你要放弃这机会  坐在沙发上
and you're gonna give it up to sit on the couch
跟我一起看《新鲜王子》吗
and watch Fresh Prince with me?
什么
What?
我觉得你该好好想想
I just think you should consider
你在给你的女儿立下什么样的榜样
what kind of example you're setting for your daughter.
这是怎么回事
What's going on around here?
我知道
I know, I know.
我去里面解释  谢谢你们
I'll explain inside. Thank you.
你妈妈很幸运
Your mom's lucky.
天上发孩子时
When they were handing out kids,
给了她最坚强的一个
they gave her the toughest one.
捣蛋中尉
Lieutenant Trouble.
你记得了
You remembered.
那是我的吗
Is that mine?
不
No, no.
你留着吧  等我回来再说
You hang on to it until I come back.
但有件事我需要你帮忙
But there is something that I need your help with.
我不能再穿克里人的颜色了
I can't wear these Kree colors anymore.
而因为你显然是这里唯一
And since you are obviously the only person around here
有时尚感的人
with any sense of style...
不行
No.
绝对不行
Definitely not.
既然我们是一队的
Well, since we're on the same team...
我看上去如何
How do I look?
靓丽
Fresh.
你怎么才来
What took you so long?
我很好  多谢关心
I'm fine. Thanks for asking.
-PRY46B  -不  不说密码了
- PRY46-B... - No, no codes.
这系统不可靠了  我们都知道了
That system is fallible, as we've learned.
好吧  那我们开始吧
Okay, then let's do this.
我与至高智慧密谈时  看到的是谁
Who do I see when I commune with the Supreme Intelligence?
你最崇拜尊敬的人吧
The person you most admire and respect, I'd guess.
但你绝不会告诉我是谁的
But you would never tell me who.
你对哈拉最早的记忆是什么
And what is your earliest memory of Hala?
输血
The transfusion.
蓝血流过我的血管
Blue blood running through my veins.
谁的血
Whose blood?
流过她血管的是我的血
That's my blood that's coursing through her veins.
你把她怎么了
What have you done with her?
你太迟了
You're too late.
她知道了
She knows?
罗南  斯库鲁人已潜入了C53
Ronan, Skrulls have infiltrated C-53.
马上来
Come at once.
为了全体克里人  指挥官
For the good of all Kree, Commander,
入侵者会被根除的
the infestation will be eradicated.
高度500  还在攀升
Passing 500 and climbing.
你真的不该把那玩意放腿上
You know, you really shouldn't have that thing on your lap.
我们跟你的联盟没那么可靠
Our little alliance with you is tenuous at best.
只要它还能吓到你
And as long as he continues to freak you out...
就像这样
like that...
嗯  我就要继续
yeah, I'm gonna keep giving him
爱它抱它  让它满意
all the loves and hugs that he needs, right?
我能问你件事吗
Can I ask you something?
你可以想变成什么变成什么
Do you just turn into anything you want?
我得先看到
Well, I have to see it first.
你们都能吗
Can you all do it?
从生理学上讲  是的
Physiologically? Yeah.
但这是需要练习的
But, uh, it takes practice...
不瞒你说  还需要天赋  才能做好
and, um, dare I say it, talent to do it well.
-你能变成猫吗  -猫是什么
- Can you turn into a cat? - What's a cat?
那文件柜呢
What about a filing cabinet?
我为什么要变成文件柜
Why would I turn into a filing cabinet?
捕蝇草呢
A Venus flytrap?
如果你能变成捕蝇草
I'll give you 50 bucks right now
我这就给你50块
if you turn into a Venus flytrap.
超音速燃烧冲压式喷气引擎切换至核聚变引擎
Switching engines from Scramjet to Fusion.
坐稳了  各位
Buckle up, folks.
这正常吗  是太空紊流吗
Is this normal, like, space turbulence?
差不多吧
Pretty much.
锁定坐标网格
Locking in on coordinate grid.
它在哪呢
Where is it?
就在这里  肯定在这里
It's here. It's gotta be here.
那是在空空荡荡前面还是后面
Well, is it in front of all that nothing, or behind it?
去隐形启动
Decloaking activated.
玛威尔的实验室
克里帝国巡航舰
就是那个吗  能量核
Is that it? The core?
在她的笔记里  她称之为宇宙魔方
In her notes she called it the Tesseract.
劳森怎么会有这么多孩子玩具
What was Lawson doing with all this kid stuff?
方子
这里有别人
We're not alone.
塔罗斯
Talos!
他不是来找宇宙魔方的
He didn't come here for the Tesseract.
没事
It's okay.
我们不知道该怎么办
We didn't know what to do.
玛威尔警告我们无论如何都不能发信号
Mar-Vell warned us not to send a signal for any reason...
否则会被克里人找到
or the Kree would find us.
你做得对
You did the right thing.
没事
It's okay, it's okay.
她没事  她是个朋友
She's all right. She's a friend.
我不会伤害你们的
I am not gonna hurt you.
是她让我找到你们的
She led me to you.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我之前不知道
I didn't know.
卡罗尔
Carol.
这是战争
This is war.
我手上也沾满了鲜血
My hands are filthy from it, too.
但我们走到了这一步
But we're here now.
你找到了我的家人
You found my family.
这只是个开始
This is just the beginning.
我们还有数千人  散落在银河系各处
There are thousands of us separated from each other...
彼此分离
scattered throughout the galaxy.
太空入侵者  最高分
如果我同一台弹球机玩六年
If I played the same pinball machine for six years...
也能打出很高的分
I'd have some high scores, too.
亲近敌人
Fraternizing with the enemy?
你把你的制服怎么了
What did you do to your uniform?
他们控制了她的心智  就像我们猜的那样
They got in her head. Just like we thought.
至高智慧能恢复她的心智
The Supreme Intelligence will set her straight.
你看得到他们不是战士
You can see they're not soldiers.
放了他们吧  把我抓走
Let 'em go. You can have me.
能量核呢
And the core?
你骗了我
You lied to me.
我让你成了最好的自己
I made you the best version of yourself.
赐予你的也能收回
What's given can be taken away.
过去  快走
Back here! Move, move!
过去  趴下
Get over here. Get down!
快走  走
Let's go! Go, move!
她来了
There she is.
看来你在C53上的经历让你想起了曾经
Seems like your time on C-53 jogged the old memory.
这件外套
This jacket.
真是帅爆了
It's killer, by the way.
音乐  真不错
The music. It's a nice touch.
放我走
Let me out.
不行
No can do.
如果你伤害他们  我就把你烧毁
If you hurt them, I will burn you to the ground.
用什么呢
With what exactly?
你的能力来自我们
Your power comes from us.
这能力不是你们给的
You didn't give me these powers.
是那场爆炸
The blast did.
但你一直都不够强大
And yet, you've never had the strength
不能自己控制好
to control them on your own.
物种  噬元兽
Species: Flerken.
威胁程度  高
Threat: high.
它是只猫  不是汉尼拔·莱克特
It's a cat, not Hannibal Lecter.
物种  人类男性
Species: human male.
威胁程度  几乎为零
Threat: low to none.
那玩意显然是坏了
That thing's clearly busted.
把噬元兽装上氦核飞船
Load the Flerken onto the Helion.
把其他的丢进太空
Eject the others into space.
你做得很棒  王牌
You did good, Ace.
因为你
Thanks to you...
那些险恶的变形人
those insidious shapeshifters
再不能威胁我们的边境了
will threaten our borders no more.
我以前相信过你的谎言
I used to believe your lies...
但斯库鲁人只是在为建立家园而战
but the Skrulls are just fighting for a home.
你想摧毁他们
You're talking about destroying them
就因为他们不肯屈从你的规矩
because they won't submit to your rule.
我也不会屈服的
And neither will I.
是我们发现了你  我们把你接纳为我们的一员
We found you. We embraced you as our own.
你们绑架了我
You stole me.
让我远离家乡  家人  朋友
From my home, my family, my friends.
你的努力真是可爱
It's cute how hard you try.
但记住
But remember...
没有我们
without us...
放弃吧  卡罗尔
Give it up, Carol.
别起来了
Stay down!
你是弱小的
...you're weak.
你开太快了  你得慢点
You're going too fast! You need to go slow!
你是不完美的
You're flawed.
你是想害死自己吗
Are you trying to kill yourself?
无助的
Helpless.
你太情绪化  好弱
You're too emotional and so weak.
你不该来这里
You don't belong out here!
是我们救了你
We saved you.
-控制住  -我说了  卡罗尔
- Control it. - I told you, Carol.
他们绝不会让你飞的
They'll never let you fly.
这不是小姑娘的游戏
This ain't a game for little girls.
你吻技好生硬
You kiss like a horse.
你一周都坚持不住  丹弗斯
You won't last a week, Danvers.
没有我们  你只是人类
Without us, you're only human.
你说对了
You're right.
我只是人类
I'm only human.
在哈拉上  你重生了  成为了
On Hala, you were reborn...
弗斯
Vers.
我叫卡罗尔
My name is Carol.
她想挣脱出来
She's trying to break out.
我一直绑着一只手作战
I've been fighting with one arm tied behind my back.
但如果我
But what happens when...
终于挣脱开会怎样
I'm finally set free?
你知道你在发光吧
You know you're glowing, right?
回头解释
I'll explain it later.
拿走宇宙魔方
Take the Tesseract.
留下午餐盒
Leave the lunchbox.
-我吗  -对
- Me? - Yes.
我可不碰那玩意
I'm not touching that thing.
要我给你找副防热手套吗
You want me to get you an oven mitt?
带斯库鲁人上夸式战斗机飞走
Get the Skrulls on the Quadjet and go.
带上噬元兽
Take the Flerken with you.
-那你呢  -我给你们争取时间
- What about you? - I'll buy you some time!
我要把你抱起来了
I'm picking you up now.
我相信你不会吃了我
I'm trusting you not to eat me.
你们好啊
Guys.
为宇宙魔方掰腕子啊
Arm wrestle for the Tesseract?
我以前还觉得你挺逗
I used to find you amusing.
我们做个了结吧
Let's put an end to this.
好吧
Okay.
乖喵喵
Good kitty.
你一直都知道
You knew all along.
所以我们才从不一起玩吗
Is that why we never hung out?
不  我就是不喜欢你
No, I just never liked you.
来啦
Incoming!
着什么急
In a hurry?
别逼我这么做
Don't make me do this.
那好
Okay.
快点  吃了他们
Come on, do your thing!
来啊
Come on!
真是的  咕咕
Damn it, Goose.
选好边吧
Pick a side.
把他们也带去机库
Take them to the hangar, too.
我们把他们都丢进太空
We'll blast them all into space.
别激动
Play it cool.
就像在哈瓦那时那样
Just like Havana.
你拿到那东西了吗
Do you have the thing?
被噬元兽猫吃了
Flerken kitty ate it.
快走
Come on, move!
Move!
看我的行事
Follow my lead.
遮住她的眼睛
Cover her eyes.
上船
Onto the ship!
快走  快走
Let's go! Let's go!
好个移花接木
Nice diversion.
我真以为我放进去了
I could have swore I put it in there.
米涅瓦  开战机击落他们
Minn-Erva, take them down in the drop ship.
好的
On it.
你没事吧  朋友
You all right, friend?
好极了
Never better.
有敌机追来了
We got a bogey coming in hot.
好啊
Yes!
那是什么鬼
What the hell was that?
发射弹道导弹弹头
Deploy ballistic warheads.
这不可能
That's impossible.
C53没有能摧毁我们弹头的
C-53 doesn't have a defense system
足够先进的防御系统
advanced enough to destroy our warheads.
那不是他们的防御系统  罗南
That's not their defense system, Ronan.
干掉她
Take her down.
回跳跃点
Return to the jump point.
我们改日再回来带走武器
We'll be back for the weapon.
能量核吗
The core?
是她
The woman.
我真为你骄傲
I'm so proud of you.
自那天
You've come a long way
我在湖边发现你  你进步了好多
since I found you that day by the lake.
但你能克制住你的情绪
But can you keep your emotions in check
直到打败我吗
long enough to take me on?
还是你仍会如以往那样被情绪左右
Or will they get the better of you as always?
我一直对你说
I always told you...
等你可以
you'll be ready
凭自身实力打倒我  你就真准备好了
the day you can knock me down as yourself.
这一刻终于来了
This is that moment.
这就是见分晓的时刻  弗斯
This is that moment, Vers!
停下那些花里胡哨的
Turn off the light show...
向我证明  你可以光明正大地打败我...
and prove to me you can beat me without...
我不用向你证明什么
I have nothing to prove to you.
目的地  哈拉
Destination: Hala.
我不能空手而归
I can't go back empty-handed.
你不会空手而归
You won't be empty-handed.
我会让你带句话回去
I'm sending you with a message.
告诉至高智慧  我会去终结一切
Tell the Supreme Intelligence that I'm coming to end it.
战争  谎言  所有一切
The war. The lies. All of it.
你不能那么做
You can't do this.
真悬啊  是吧  咕咕
That was a close call, huh, Goosey?
那些坏蛋还在你里面吗
Those bad guys still in there somewhere?
我的噬元兽啊
Mother Flerken!
-你没事吧  -嗯
- You okay? - Yeah.
就是抓了一下而已
It's just a scratch.
不
No.
真不敢相信你卷入了一场最酷的肉搏战
I can't believe you got in the raddest dogfight ever...
而我没看到
and I missed it.
要我说  你到的正是时候
I'd say you arrived just in time.
你飞得真的很漂亮
Some nifty flying you did out there.
神盾局总是需要你这样的好飞行员
S.H.I.E.L.D. could always use a good pilot like you.
我会考虑的
I'll consider it...
只要你不再说我的飞行"漂亮"
as long as you never call my flying "nifty" again.
你的眼睛怎么样了
How's your eye?
每秒都在愈合
Getting better every second.
我想问清楚
Just so I'm clear...
索拉
you were Soh-Larr...
-和那个神盾特工都是你  -凯勒
- and the S.H.I.E.L.D. agent? - Keller.
他把我上司绑了起来  盗用了他的身份
He tied my boss up, stole his identity.
我只是借了他的脸  我不是贼
I borrowed his likeness. I'm no thief.
是有点像盗窃
It is a little like stealing.
你是谁那边的
Whose side are you on here?
你康复前都可以在这里养伤
You're good to go here until you recover...
但你和你家人得换副新模样
but you and your family are gonna need a new look.
我可以继续做你上司
I could go back to being your boss.
千万别
Please don't.
怎么了  我喜欢他那双漂亮的蓝眼睛
Come on. I loved sporting his beautiful blue eyes.
说什么呢  你们的眼睛最漂亮了
No way. You guys have the best eyes.
-永远别变你的眼睛  -她的眼睛是很美
- Don't ever change your eyes. - She has beautiful eyes.
多谢你了
That's very sweet of you.
我想努力不慌乱
I was trying not to panic...
我会帮你们找到家的
I'll help you find a home.
完成玛威尔的心愿
Finish what Mar-Vell started.
他们可以跟我们住这儿
They can stay here with us.
不是吗  妈妈
Can't they, Mom?
他们在这里不安全的  宝贝
They won't be safe here, baby.
卡罗尔阿姨是对的
Auntie Carol's right.
他们得有自己的家
They need their own home.
我很快就会回来
I'll be back before you know it.
或许我可以飞上天  跟你碰头
Or maybe I could fly up and meet you halfway?
那你得学会像卡罗尔阿姨那样发光
Only if you learn to glow like your Auntie Carol.
或许我可以建艘飞船
Or maybe I'll build a spaceship.
-你又说不准  -是啊
- You don't know. - He doesn't.
把宇宙魔方留在地球上
Keep the Tesseract on Earth.
藏好
Hidden.
你确定那是马威会想要的吗
You sure that's what Marvel would want?
是玛威尔
Mar-Vell.
我就那么说的
That's what I said.
是两个词  玛  威尔
It's two words. Mar. Vell.
玛威尔
Mar-Vell.
"马威"听上去好多了
"Marvel" sounds a lot better.
就像惊艳合唱团
You know, like the Marvelettes.
没印象吗
Not ringing any bells?
继续唱  或许我会想起来
Keep singing. Maybe it'll come back to me.
我给它升级了
I upgraded it.
信号范围能至少覆盖几个星系了
Range should be a couple galaxies, at least.
怎么  你觉得我会给你打骚扰电话吗
What? You think I'm gonna crank call you?
仅限紧急情况
For emergencies only, okay?
好吧
Well...
如果你再路过这个星系
if you're ever passing back through this galaxy...
务必喊我一声
be sure to give a brother a shout.
我们洗干净了番茄酱的污迹
We got the ketchup stain off.
谢谢  捣蛋中尉
Thanks, Lieutenant Trouble.
我也不愿意道别
It's hard for me to say goodbye, too.
去吧
Go on.
保护者计划
很高兴你回来了  长官
Glad to have you back, sir.
这是寄给您的
This came for you.
是真的吗
So, is it true?
克里人烧毁了你的眼睛
That the Kree burned your eye out...
因为你不肯交出宇宙魔方
because you refused to give them the Tesseract?
我既不能承认也不能否认这种说法
I will neither confirm nor deny the facts of that story.
明白
Understood.
很遗憾
I'm sorry to report
我们仍尚未找到宇宙魔方
that we still haven't found the Tesseract.
它肯定会出现的
I'm sure it'll turn up somewhere.
等出现了我会通知您的
I'll let you know when it does.
然后呢
Then what?
长官
Sir?
我们完全不知道还存在怎样的跨星系威胁
We have no idea what other intergalactic threats are out there.
而我们的单人女子保安
And our one-woman security force
还要优先处理宇宙另一边的问题
had a prior commitment on the other side of the universe.
单靠神盾局不足以保护我们
S.H.I.E.L.D. alone can't protect us.
我们需要找到更多的
We need to find more.
更多武器吗
More weapons?
更多英雄
More heroes.
你觉得还能找到其他她这样的人
You think you can find others like her?
我们找到了她  而且还是没在找的时候
We found her, and we weren't even looking.
休息一下吧  长官
Get some rest, sir.
你要做个重要决定呢
You got a big decision to make.
"复仇者"卡罗尔·丹弗斯上尉
复仇者计划
惊奇队长
全球失踪人数
肯尼亚失踪人数
这真是场噩梦
This is a nightmare.
我做的噩梦都比这强
I've had better nightmares.
那玩意停了
So, that thing just stopped doing
虽然也不知它在干什么
whatever the hell it was doing.
什么情况
What do we got?
它在发送的信号终于停止了
Whatever signal it was sending finally crapped out.
我们不是外接了电池吗
I thought we bypassed the battery.
是的
We did.
电还插着呢  它就是停了
It's still plugged in. It just stopped.
重启  再发一次信号
Reboot it. Send the signal again.
我们都不知道这是什么
We don't even know what this is.
弗瑞知道  照做吧
Fury did. Just do it, please.
一有信号就告诉我
You tell me the second you get a signal.
我想知道接收信号的人是谁
I wanna know who's on the other end of that thing.
弗瑞人呢
Where's Fury?
惊奇队长将在《复仇者联盟4：终局之战》中回归